Guide to the University Archives Photograph Collection, Glass Negatives and Lantern Slides, circa 1890-circa 1960 UA 023.031 UA 023.031
Special Collections Research Center
- North Carolina State University Campus, Series 7
  - Ricks Hall
    - Plate E. G. Macon for 1932 - 4-H Calf, Wake County - Mr. Harrell, Ricks Hall, No. 1 - 2 copies, Set #13 (Cardbox 3, Envelope 76)
  - Riddick Engineering Laboratories
    - Architects drawing of Riddick Building - Engineering Research - Set #18 (Cardbox 5, Envelope 13)
    - Riddick Engineering Laboratories Building - Engineering Research - Set #18 (Cardbox 5, Envelope 14)
    - Chemical Engineering laboratories area - Engineering Research - Set #18 (Cardbox 5, Envelope 48)
    - Civil Engineering - portion of testing laboratory - Engineering Research - Set #18 (Cardbox 5, Envelope 38)
    - Civil Engineering - hydraulic lab - miniature open channel - Engineering Research - Set #18 (Cardbox 5, Envelope 39)
    - Civil Engineering - hydraulic lab - Pelton wheel and v-notch wier - Engineering Research - Set #18 (Cardbox 5, Envelope 40)
    - Chemical Engineering - view of unit operations lab - Engineering Research - Set #18 (Cardbox 5, Envelope 41)
    - Chemical Engineering - view of unit operations lab with people - Engineering Research - Set #18 (Cardbox 5, Envelope 42)
    - Chemical Engineering - Technical Analysis Lab with people - Engineering Research, Set #18 (Cardbox 8, Envelope 43)
    - Riddick Laboratories - 3rd floor diagram - Engineering Research, Set #18 (Cardbox 8, Envelope 44)
  - Tompkins Hall
    - Tompkins, circa 1914 - NCSU Campus [slide cracked] (Cardbox 16, Envelope 24)
    - Tompkins Hall with cars in front - Engineering Research - Set #18 (Cardbox 5, Envelope 44)
  - Winston Hall
    - Winston Hall - Physical and Mathematical Sciences School - Dean's Office [broken/cracked slide box] (Cardbox 16, Envelope 9)
    - Civil Engineering Building - Engineering Research - Set #18 (Cardbox 5, Envelope 16)
    - Winston Hall - Engineering Research - Set #18 (Cardbox 5, Envelope 21)
  - Withers Hall
    - Withers Hall - chemistry - with cars in front - Engineering Research - Set #18 (Cardbox 5, Envelope 43)
    - Agriculture School - Chemistry Department - Chemistry Lab (glass is chipped on top left corner) - for photograph see Agriculture School - Chemistry Department (Cardbox 18, Envelope 4)
- People, Series 8
  - Clubs and Camps
    - Members of North Carolina Agricultural Clubs attending short course at A & M College, Raleigh, North Carolina - 17-20 August 1915 (17) - Set #15 (Cardbox 4, Envelope 8)
    - (no. 9) African American camp on beach in North Carolina, circa 1920s - Hand Colored Slides, Numbered Series (Cardbox 10, Envelope 6)
    - (no. 10) African American Home Demonstration Club - women - North Carolina - Hand Colored Slides, Numbered Series (Cardbox 10, Envelope 7)
    - (no. 11) African American Home Demonstration Club - club market in North Carolina - Thompson's Roadside market - Hand Colored Slides, Numbered Series (Cardbox 10, Envelope 8)
  - Miscellaneous
    - Picnic (brown dots on negative) - Set #14 (Cardbox 4, Envelope 2)
    - Miscellaneous - people - Set #15 (Cardbox 4, Envelope 6)
    - Seaman A. Knapp (crack in lower left corner) - See photograph in Photograph Collection - People - Faculty, Staff, Alumni, Etc. - NCSU Campus (Cardbox 4, Envelope 27)
    - Group of men with survey equipment - Engineering Research, Set #18 (Cardbox 8, Envelope 78)
    - Person standing in field in the mountains - Hand Colored Slides, H. C. initials (Cardbox 11, Envelope 59)
    - Man in a field of snap beans in a hilly area - Hand Colored Slides, H. C. initials (Cardbox 11, Envelope 60)
    - Boy standing in corn field - Hand Colored Slides, H. C. initials (Cardbox 11, Envelope 61)
    - Two people standing in a tobacco field - Hand Colored Slides, H. C. initials (Cardbox 11, Envelope 62)
    - Man holding flowers in a field in the mountains - Hand Colored Slides, H. C. initials (Cardbox 11, Envelope 63)
    - Men standing in a field - Hand Colored Slides, H. C. initials (Cardbox 11, Envelope 64)
    - Man with horse and colt in a field - Hand Colored Slides, H. C. initials (Cardbox 11, Envelope 65)
    - Man and a donkey in a field - Hand Colored Slides, H. C. initials (Cardbox 11, Envelope 66)
    - Two people in front of a house (see 68) - Hand Colored Slides, H. C. initials (Cardbox 11, Envelope 67)
    - Person standing at the edge of the woods - Hand Colored Slides, H. C. initials (Cardbox 11, Envelope 69)
    - Boy standing by trees - Hand Colored Slides, H. C. initials (Cardbox 11, Envelope 70)
    - 2 men with blackberry plants by the water, circa 1920s - Hand Colored Slides, People (Cardbox 12, Envelope 157)
    - Large group of people in front of a chicken house (probably a farm tour), circa 1920s - Hand Colored Slides, People (Cardbox 12, Envelope 158)
    - Man standing on a hillside - Hand Colored Slides, People (Cardbox 12, Envelope 159)
    - Group of twenty-one boys in front of brick building - Hand Colored Slides, agricultural ext. & research, Set #19 (Cardbox 13, Envelope 10)
    - Group of five boys and three swine (slide is cracked) - See cracked and broken slides - Hand Colored Slides, agricultural ext. & research, Set #19 (Cardbox 13, Envelope 21)
    - A group of people in front of a building - Hand Colored Slides, agricultural ext. & research, Set #19 (Cardbox 13, Envelope 22)
    - Three women dressed up - Hand Colored Slides, agricultural ext. & research, Set #19 (Cardbox 13, Envelope 24)
  - Students
    - Two men and woman standing outside looking at books (brown discoloration) - Set #14 (Cardbox 4, Envelope 1)
    - Students in a classroom - NCSU Campus (Cardbox 4, Envelope 10)
    - Students in class (emulsion is wearing in speckles) - See neg. #352 - See Photographs - students - NCSU Campus (Cardbox 4, Envelope 11)
    - Surveying in a field - NCSU Campus (Cardbox 4, Envelope 12)
    - Military, p. 131 of the 1916 Agromeck "The Regiment" - See neg. #24 - NCSU Campus (Cardbox 4, Envelope 26)
    - Class scene, with nine people - NCSU Nuclear Reactor, Set #16 (Cardbox 4, Envelope 10)
    - Horticulture - students in greenhouse - for photograph see - Agriculture school - Horticulture - Hand Colored Slides, agriculture school (Cardbox 13, Envelope 1)
    - Poultry Science Department - North Carolina A & M students looking at chickens - Hand Colored Slides, agriculture school (Cardbox 13, Envelope 2)
    - People - Students - Students in Textile Class (slide is broken) (Cardbox 18, Envelope 1)
- Water and Dams, Series 9
  - (no. 12) T.V.A. area - dams are listed - map of Tennessee, Western North Carolina, SW VA, Southern KY, N. Miss., N. Alabama, N. GA, NW SC, and E. MO. - Hand Colored Slides, Numbered Series (Cardbox 10, Envelope 9)
  - Stream with small fall - Hand Colored Slides, H. C. initials (Cardbox 11, Envelope 56)
- Photographic Prints and Manuscript Material, Series 10; 0.25 Linear feet; 1 archival half box
  - Prints - Grape Study - Set #17 (Cardbox 19, Envelope 1)
  - Prints - Cow and campus, Set #13 (Cardbox 19, Envelope 2)
  - Prints - Agricultural ext. & research - Corn (Cardbox 19, Envelope 3)
  - Prints - Agricultural ext. & research - Corn - Extra Photographs (Cardbox 19, Envelope 4)
  - Materials from original storage containers (Cardbox 19, Envelope 5)
  - Examples of original storage envelopes (Cardbox 19, Envelope 6)